Finding Aid for Cook Brothers Printing Company (Hastings, Mich.) records, 1890-1945
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Cook Brothers Printing Company (Hastings, Mich.) records 1890-1945
Cook Brothers Printing Company (Hastings, Mich.).
30 oversize volumes
851497 BB Outsize
Publishers of the Hastings Banner; financial records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was the gift of Richard Cook (donor no. 3240 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
The Cook Brothers Printing Company was owned and operated by Marshall L. Cook and William Randolph Cook. This company was responsible for the printing of the Hastings Banner newspaper and other printing jobs.
The records of the firm are exclusively financial and include cash books, advertising books, job books, ledgers, an inventory, and monthly statements of accounts.
Subjects:
Business records.; Hastings banner.; Hastings (Mich.); American newspapers--Michigan--Hastings.; Printing industry--Michigan--Hastings.
Contributors:
Cook, Marshall L., 1858-1955.; Cook, William Randolph, 1866-1946.
- Cash Book, 15 voulmes (Volume 1)
  - March 2, 1908-March 31, 1909
  - April 1, 1909-April 29, 1911
  - May 1, 1911-April 3, 1913
  - April 7, 1913-March 27, 1915
  - March 29, 1915-January 30, 1917
  - February 1, 1917-June 30, 1919
  - July 2, 1919-May 17, 1921
  - May 18, 1921-May 31, 1923
  - June 1, 1923-June 10, 1925
  - June 11, 1925-May 31, 1927
  - June 1, 1927-June 22, 1929
  - June 24, 1929-September 30, 1931
  - October 1, 1931-July 31, 1934
  - August 1, 1934-December 31, 1936
  - January 2, 1937-November 12, 1938
- Advertising Book, 5 volumes (Volume 2)
  - April 18, 1906-September 28, 1910
  - October 4, 1910-April 30, 1914
  - May 7, 1914-October 25, 1917
  - November 1, 1917-December 30, 1925
  - January 6, 1926-October 31, 1934
- Job Book, 6 volumes (Volume 3)
  - February 1908-December 1913
  - January 1914-September 1919
  - September 1919-July 1925
  - August 1925-January 1934
  - February 1934-December 1939
  - January 1940-June 1945
- Other records, 4 volumes (Volume 4)
  - Ledger, January 1890-July 1898
  - Ledger, July 1898-March 1905
  - Inventory, 1912 (revised 1914)
  - Monthly Statements of accounts, 1907-1910
Related Material
The Bentley Library also has the personal, business, and political papers of Marshall L. Cook and William Randolph Cook.